[engine starts]
-[Jerry] This is a 1969 Pontiac GTO.
-[engine revving]
But not just any GTO.
This... is the Judge.
[rock music playing]
The name "GTO" was stolen
from the Ferrari GTO of the early '60s.
But in America, in 1969, we thought,
"Ah, they're all the way over in Italy.
-They'll never catch us."
-[tires screech]
And "the Judge" was
from Sammy Davis Jr.'s character
on Rowan & Martin's Laugh-In.
Here comes the judge!
[Jerry] I guess in 1969,
Pontiac's attitude was,
"Copyright?
Screw it, we'll decide what's right."
[engine starts and revs]
Especially with a blacked-out grille,
hideaway headlights,
a tach on the hood, a rear spoiler,
and open-hood scoops into a four-barrel,
370-horsepower V-8.
[engine revving]
-[Howard] Hello?
-[Jerry] Howard?
[Howard] Jerry Seinfeld. Oh, my God.
[Jerry] Remember when you were trying
to make it and I came on your show?
-[Howard] Right, right, and I--
-[Jerry] Or was it the other way around?
[Howard] I don't know. It doesn't matter.
I gotta be honest.
I don't wanna go
to a coffee shop with you.
[Jerry] I don't give a damn. You're stuck.
-[Howard] You have nothing prepared?
-[Jerry] Nothing.
[Howard] I can't believe we're doing this.
[Jerry] I'm Jerry Seinfeld,
and this is
Comedians in Cars Getting Coffee.
A GTO is for a guy that wants
to tell the world,
"I will not be going quietly."
Which is why it's a perfect car
for my guest this week, Mr. Howard Stern,
who, according to him,
is the greatest radio broadcaster
of all time.
[tires screech]
Let's get the coffee
and get this over with.
Look at the people rejoicing
that we're here.
This is fun. Let's go.
[Howard] Here's where it started for me.
This radio was everything to my father.
He would ignore me the entire time.
He would tell me to shush the whole time
and ignore me.
-And I became enamored with radio.
-Wow.
I could get my father's attention,
if I could get in that box
and get on the radio.
And so this was my way
of getting my dad's attention.
Hey, I'm opening up. Hi, ladies.
I feel this is the most unimportant show
in show business that I'm on right now.
Then that's another win for me.
I got you on the most unimportant show
in show business.
Well,
I'm honored that you asked me, actually.
-Really?
-Yeah. I really am, because I admire you.
-[softly] Thank you.
-And I love what you do.
I'm a fan of musicians and comics
and all these people,
and I love doing an interview
with people like yourself
-or Graham Nash or Paul McCartney.
-Mm-hmm.
I would say that therapy helped me
to appreciate what I have.
[Jerry] Do you think therapy
could help me?
[Howard] I absolutely do.
-What could I possibly be better at?
-A lot of things.
Do I seem to have problems?
Can you pee in front of other men?
Do you have trouble?
-No.
-I have a huge issue with that.
I can't. If you and I had to go pee,
it would be terrible.
-Let's go pee together today.
-No. I'm not doing it.
-Well, you've talked to me privately.
-Yeah.
It's awkward talking to me, right?
It's uncomfortable.
-No, I like talking... Yeah.
-Really?
I think people just want to get away.
-From you?
-Yeah. Unless we're on the radio.
Maybe if you didn't have the little hairs
in front of the lens of the glasses.
-What am I gonna do about it?
-You might seem more open.
Maybe I'm hiding.
You're like a hip
Wicked Witch of the West.
Look at this Yenta here, Howard,
on the phone.
Look at the bent hand...
Is there any difference
between a baby with a bottle
and a woman walking, a grown woman
who can't [beeps] walk five steps
without her cell phone on?
Everybody's proud of themselves.
Everybody thinks their life
is the big thing that's going on.
Right. Even though we know my life
is the big thing going on.
-Why would they think that?
-[laughs]
What do you want to do, do you think,
the last year of your life?
I don't know.
I'm obsessed with that, are you?
-No.
-Just give me some time.
I'm in love with my wife,
I do want to spend time with her.
You're like a woman to me
in a sense that...
-I don't have to be...
-That sounds like a Graham Nash song.
No, because you're a comedian,
every minute you're evaluating.
-You're judgmental.
-That's right.
The comedian studies himself.
-Yes.
-The actor studies other people.
-That's true.
-The comedian
wants to be himself.
The actor wants to be anyone
-but themselves.
-You're so true.
Because I feel tortured.
I'm so self-conscious, so self-aware.
-I would like...
-You're not tortured.
...to see you make some progress.
-But you don't experience that.
-Not so self-conscious.
-Okay. It's not about your looks, Howard.
-But you are...
Don't you get that by now?
-Nobody cares...
-Yeah, but...
...what your hair looks like.
That's exactly why I go to therapy.
-I understand that intellectually.
-I'm telling you,
you can go to me,
you don't need the therapy.
Let me ask you something.
You didn't answer my question.
-Wait a second.
-You're not a good talk-show guest.
When you did your sitcom, okay?
If America hadn't tuned in,
wouldn't you have cared
what America thought?
Of course. Yes. That's different
than caring about my hair.
-It's the same exact thing.
-It's the complete opposite!
You're saying that we want to get
to a point as people, as adults...
As long as we feel good
about how we feel...
No, no, no. You misunderstood me.
So, on the radio, should I worry
about what other people think?
-Yes. You should...
-Should I worry about what I think?
You should worry
that they're enjoying the show or not.
-Same as worrying about your hair.
-But if people like my stupid hair
-or how fat I am.
-It's the same [beeps] thing.
Your hair is not an achievement.
Yours perhaps is,
but most people's hair is not.
My hair is an achievement.
Did you have a hair person
before this show?
-Absolutely, I did. No, I'm--
-You're a radio guy.
I mean, honestly, I want to know
how you are sexually.
-Why? This is another gay thing.
-Well, because it's interesting.
No, stop it.
Why is everything gay with you?
I like "gay."
I'm not comfortable talking about this.
That's why this is great.
[laughs]
This is why your show
is the top show on the Internet.
[Jerry claps]
[Howard] Let's go.
It's enough already.
I'm worn out from you.
That's an accomplishment.
Hey, now! See? People are nice.
[Jerry] If you could have anything here,
what would you have?
-I like this. The chocolate...
-[Jerry] Really?
-[Jerry] Chocolate cake.
-[Howard] Chocolate anything.
Chocolate with peanut butter. Oh.
-Oh, let's do it.
-Let's do it.
-We're gonna get him a brownie.
-No.
I don't want a brownie.
I'm not gonna eat it.
-Don't waste your time.
-[waiter] Coffee?
-Yes.
-[Howard] He's gonna have coffee.
-I'm gonna have a cup of hot water.
-[waiter] Fine. I'll be right back.
Oh, God! This is like being with my aunt
from the old country.
How long can you actually,
physically stay focused on the kids?
I can't play Monopoly.
I cannot play Chutes and Ladders.
I'd rather someone shoot me on a ladder.
Sorry!, to me,
is the most perfectly named game.
I've never felt so sorry.
Your career is a victory over the self.
It wasn't the business.
It wasn't other people.
It wasn't your relationships,
your wife, whatever.
None of that was the biggest obstacle.
It was you. You conquered yourself.
But when I evaluate myself as a radio guy,
I think I'm the best that ever lived.
-[laughs]
-Ever.
Are you better than Jay Leno
as a stand-up?
That's a stupid question.
Do you think you're one of the best
stand-ups that ever lived?
-Would you put yourself in the top five?
-Comedy is more personal than food.
Someone either hits you funny
or they don't.
I never gave a [beeps]
I would go on and say
whatever the hell was--
Well, you're alone in the room.
-True. It's different.
-You just noticed?
When he goes on talk shows now...
Okay, all right, let's not get
into character assassination, okay?
-Who are you, Jesus?
-[laughs]
Calm down. I want to get negative.
Let me go there.
What kind of interviewer are you?
You have to let me get negative.
You have to let me be me.
-You be you and I'll be me.
-Great idea.
-You're so judgmental. I told you.
-I am.
-[Howard] Donald Trump.
-Do you like him?
I think he's one
of the best radio guests ever.
He comes on, and he will say whatever
-is on his mind.
-Yeah.
Some of the best interviews with him,
that you would never do this, but...
He sits down and I go,
"Donald,
I don't care about financial advice,
I don't care about that."
-Gee, I wonder why.
-I say,
"Talk to me about women." [clears throat]
And I will name women
and he will evaluate them
on a scale of one to ten.
-And he is brutal.
-He's brutal.
Who don't you like, then?
Let's see you get a little negative.
I don't wanna hear myself
talk like that.
I'm not interested in what you like.
I wanna hear you say it.
-That's good.
-Who cares? I can't believe you.
This is what makes the great Howard Stern.
I'm having a good time.
-You're having fun.
-Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I think I'm your best interview.
Would you like to play God with shows
and make shows, and say,
"I like this guy, I want to do this"?
How come you haven't done that?
I had a production company
and I had ten shows.
Sold and in production.
And I walked away from it.
There's nothing more exciting
than the announcement.
"Howard Stern now
is the head of his own network."
-Or whatever. Some big announcement.
-Yeah.
That's a great high.
But then you have to go out
and get it done.
-Right.
-And then you have no life.
And that's the problem.
I love the announcement.
-It's so funny how it works.
-Yeah.
You get that thing,
and you don't want it.
-No.
-Why is life so [beeps] twisted like that?
I don't know.
I figured you had the answer.
Do you have trouble relating to people?
Do you feel you're fully involved,
when you're around people?
I'm sorry, I wasn't...
See, I'm sitting here thinking
you're really not enjoying this,
and you're disappointed in this.
-But that's you.
-That's why I see a shrink.
But when I tell you that you're wrong,
-you believe me, right?
-No. No.
Because I'm too nice a guy?
I don't think of you as a nice guy.
-Thank you for that. [laughs]
-I think you are very brutally honest,
and I think that you can be brutal.
I'm the nice guy sitting at this table
and you are absolutely mean.
You just made my day.
-Sell me the idea of therapy.
-You would sit down...
For me the catalyst was my relationship
with my wife wasn't going well,
things were falling apart,
and I needed guidance.
That's great for you, but what about me?
There's something going on.
It's written all over your face.
Everyone sees it.
I would've loved if my father had sat me
down and just said, "How are you?
-How are you feeling?"
-Right, right.
It seems like such a small thing.
-But it's huge.
-How are you doing?
That does touch me.
Because that's something
that I would enjoy.
I think.
Although I'm so well-defended
against that.
I see through your defenses.
Did you have a good relationship
with your father?
Yeah, I mean, I didn't expect much.
Right. By the way, I love my father.
A guy of his generation
didn't know how to go there and say...
-He was so busy working.
-Yes.
But as a kid, it would've been nice...
I don't usually say this,
but you're right, it would've been nice.
That's the gift I want to give
to my children.
"Go out. I don't care
if you're working at a Wendy's.
Be greatest at it.
Just take such pride in it."
There's no "greatest" at Wendy's.
Tell me I have a shot that
we'll have a brownie.
-Get the brownie.
-I'm not gonna do it by myself.
-All right, I'll have some.
-We're gonna share a brownie.
-[waiter] Want me to cut it?
-We'll do it.
I think it would be a little too romantic
if we do it.
[Howard] No, we're not cutters...
-We were...
-No, we weren't...
I don't want to be romantic.
[Jerry] You just want to know
how I am in bed.
-I'm excited.
-[beeps] my whole diet up.
-This is it. You ready?
-Look, he smells it like a Beaujolais.
-We're having a good time?
-Yes.
-I need you to tell me.
-Yeah.
[stutters] What are we shooting, a movie?
Are you tired, Howard?
What else you want to know about me?
-Okay, let's get back to you.
-Yeah.
-What were we talking about?
-Cunnilingus.
[camera shutter clicks]
Hi, everybody. Welcome to
What Does it Cost with Jerry Seinfeld.
Jerry, what I'm holding
in my hand right now...
$1.29. $1.79.
-It's $1.89.
-Come on!
-How much is that?
-$2.69.
-Ninety-nine cents.
-$1.49.
$1.39. It's Campbell's
Chicken Noodle Soup, Jerry.
Eighty-nine cents. $1.29.
$2.09 for a [beeps] can of soup.
-Oh, my God. Look at this mother [beeps]
-[Jerry] There he is.
-[Howard] How much is this?
-$2.79.
-$5.79.
-Most men
that have just regular jobs
don't know what these things cost.
Don't make it seem
like I'm out of touch.
-You should be in touch.
-Why?
-[Howard] This is dumb.
-[Jerry] Let's go.
In your city office, do you have
a lot of mementos of your career?
-A couple.
-What do you have hanging on the walls?
I'll tell you the greatest thing
that I've ever achieved in my career.
I was on the cover of Mad Magazine.
-I'm saying, "Hello Neuman."
-Know what's in my office?
-What?
-Mad Magazine,
the cover, I got it blown up
the size of this window.
It's all that mattered to me.
It's the most important thing.
How crazy is it
that we both feel that way?
-That's what I'm saying.
-To me that was it.
You know what it was?
That was when you found out
there were adults that were silly.
I adore Mad Magazine.
"The Judge." Hey, I'm a judge.
-You figured that out?
-Yeah.
To me, America
used to be a place
that made steel
and cars
and had giant department stores.
Now, basically we produce
amateur talent and people
that judge amateur talent.
And I hopped right in on that.
Look at that. That's...
-[Jerry] Nice.
-[Howard] You've got talent.
America's Got Talent, honey.
[laughing]
[tires screeching]
I'm thinking to cut my hair like Jerry.
-Really?
-Because it's too much.
-It's too, too much--
-You did this.
I did it already.
I'm gonna do something new.
-Hi, Toni. Are you the hair person?
-I am.
-Yeah, sorry.
-[Jerry] Want to touch him up?
-I think I look good.
-[Jerry] Gotta touch him up.
I would fluff it a little. Fluff it.
-It's getting...
-Pull it out?
Yeah, pull it out.
Come on, fix me up.
[Jerry] I don't know what the look is.
-Is it Slash or Rhea Perlman?
-[Howard sighs]